free-wordpress-theme.net 2014-02-13

# Privacy Policy | Free Wordpress Themes | Free Wordpress Themes

We can be reached via e-mail at support[at]free-wordpress-theme.net or by using our support system.  
For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes the consumers domain name, IP address and general identifying information like user name, etc. (where possible).

We collect aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit, user-specific information on what pages consumers access or visit, information volunteered by the consumer, such as poll information and/or site registrations.  
The information we collect is used to improve the content of our Web page, used to customize the content and/or layout of our page for each individual visitor, used to notify consumers about updates to our Web site.

With respect to cookies: We use cookies to store visitors preferences, record session information, such as items that consumers add to their shopping cart, customize Web page content based on visitors’ browser type or other information that the visitor sends.  
With respect to polls and surveys: We store the poll results on our database and do not provide access to any 3rd party to that data. In some cases we also use cookies to store poll preferences and protect against fraud. Although we do our best to keep our data and the poll results safe and secure, in no case should buzzer, it’s operators or owners be held responsible for any case of data loss or data theft that may occur.  
If you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, please let us know by using the options on your user profile or sending us e-mail at the above address.

If you supply us with your postal address on-line you will only receive the information for which you provided us your address.  
With respect to Ad Servers: To try and bring you offers that are of interest to you, we have relationships with other companies that we allow to place ads on our Web pages. As a result of your visit to our site, ad server companies may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address and clickstream information. For further information, consult the privacy policies of our advertisers.

From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically.  
Upon request we provide site visitors with access to a description of information that we maintain about them, you may also see and update it under your profile area on our website. Consumers can have this information corrected by sending us e-mail at the above address or updating their user profile.  
With respect to security: We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site.

We urge you to read our Privacy Policy, Terms of Use and DMCA policies before joining and using our site. By using our site you are agreeing to comply with these policies and take full and sole responsibility for your action and postings.  
If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at the above email address or by using the feedback form.  
By using our website and/or services you hereby agree to our privacy policy. If you do not agree to our policies we ask that you do not use our site.

##### All downloadable themes in our site are protected by copyrights laws, limited to our terms of use only.

###### Privacy Policy | Free Wordpress Themes Free Wordpress Themes:
